{
    "id": "44c94850d8884381a9cedec8dbd19e15",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Will you please wait here ................................. I come back?",
            "description": "Both till and until are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "till",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8960d28f642e4b21b9f5c12018308fca"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will come and see you ........................... I can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e80eae08ebbc44cc8e5dccf344768cce"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be in bed ........................ the time you get back.",
            "description": "Note the expression 'by the time'.",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7a56d9e8c9843c48b191a9348dd23e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ............................. I have the information.",
            "description": "Both 'when' and 'as soon as' are possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "when",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "80451dfaf2964f9e823d09e0bdeac8a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be relieved ............................ it is finished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "before",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8259d123fcdb4361beaacb266eeabd5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to finish it ........................ you can leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "when",
                "before",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab97be9c7b3445649400a84bea6ea909"
        },
        {
            "question": "I scraped my knee ............................. I was playing football.",
            "description": "Either 'while' or 'when' is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "when",
                "whenever"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6953ea421c234f218562f55465dfcb44"
        },
        {
            "question": "I injure myself .............................. I play football.",
            "description": "Either 'when' or 'whenever' are possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "whenever",
                "as soon as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8cbef843cd894e569fa2a715bfe38e8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you the message ............................. I receive it.",
            "description": "The expression 'the moment' can mean 'as soon as'.",
            "answers": [
                "a moment",
                "the moment"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bd4e1b204e24bf291702bfbe3d94f79"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be ready when you ..........................",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the future tense, we use a present tense in the subordinate clause to refer to future. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "will arrive",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65111021b50c439582660512eaa617d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will do it only ............................ you pay me.",
            "description": "We use 'if' to indicate condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "091712388e964b02b6748a3c37cd5d6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped playing .............................. it started raining.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. Because of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a5c5f24972840928819a88ea34bd35c"
        }
    ]
}